let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "ML is a field of AI consisting of learning algorithms that?",
  answer: " All of the above",
  options: [
      "Improve their performance",
      "At executing some task",
      "Over time with experience ",
      "  All of the above",
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: " Different learning methods does not include?",
  answer: "Introduction",
  options: [
   "Introduction",
   " Analogy",
   "Deduction",
  "Memorization"
    
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "The model will be trained with data in one single batch is known as ?",
  answer: " Both A and B",
  options: [
    " Batch learning",
    "Offline learning",
     " Both A and B",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "Which of the following are ML methods?",
  answer: "based on human supervision",
  options: [
    "based on human supervision",
    "supervised Learning",
    "semi-reinforcement Learning",
   "All of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "What is machine learning ?",
  answer: " Both A and B",
  options: [
   "  Machine learning is the science of getting computers to act without being explicitly programmed.",
"Machine Learning is a Form of AI that Enables a System to Learn from Data.",
"Both A and B",
"None of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "Machine learning is an application of __?",
  answer: "Artificial Intelligence",
  options: [
    " Blockchain",
    "Artificial Intelligence",
    "Both A and B",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
{
numb: 7, 
  question: "The term machine learning was coined in which year?",
  answer:   "1959",
  options:[
    "1958",
    "1959",
    "1960",
    "1961"
  ]
},

{
numb: 8,
question: " ___is the machine learning algorithms that can be used with unlabeled data.",   
answer:   "Clustering algorithms",
options:[
  "Instance-based algorithms",
"Regression algorithms",
"Clustering algorithms",
" All of the above"
]
},
{
numb: 9,
  question: "The Real-world machine learning use cases are ___",
  answer: "All of the above",
  options:[
    "Digital assistants",
    "Chatbots",
    "Fraud detection",
    "All of the above"
 
  ]
},
{
numb: 10,
 question: " Which among the following algorithms are used in Machine learning?",
 answer: "All of the above",
 options:[
  "K-Nearest Neighbors",
"Support Vector Machines",
"Naive Bayes",
"All of the above"
]

},

];